coinschedule.com 2018-03-09

# Coinschedule.com Privacy Policy

**The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to COINSCHEDULE.COM to help our users retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, COINSCHEDULE.COM follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for user privacy and data protection.**
* We take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of our Website’s users throughout their visiting experience. We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone, except for the efficient servicing of your Order and according to the Terms & Conditions of Sale, as they are updated from time to time and provided in our website. 
* We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users. 

**This website complies with all applicable EU laws and requirements for user privacy.**

 **NOTICE**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you and your business (personal information and/or business information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or when you submit a new ICO project to us. We use your Personal Information for five primary purposes: 

* To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. 
* To help you quickly find and access services or information. 
* To help us create content most relevant to you. 
* To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from COINSCHEDULE.COM. 
* To perform background checks and reviews that ensure our services are not used for unlawful purposes, and ensure further that while we are offering our services to you we remain fully compliant with the regulatory and legal framework within which we operate. 

**CONTACT AND COMMUNICATION**  
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk. 

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties. 

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding COINSCHEDULE.COM. products, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from COINSCHEDULE.COM. 

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of www.coinschedule.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

COINSCHEDULE.COM occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered users information about their products and services. If you do not want to receive these offers, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing materials from third parties. 

**ACCESS**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the user dashboard. There, you can: 

* View and edit personal information you have already given us. 
* Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information, or whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail. 
* Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products. 
* Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on www.coinschedule.com, your information stays with you. 

**SECURITY**  
COINSCHEDULE.COM has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honoured. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

We guarantee your transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you make transactions, or access your personal account information, you're utilizing secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available. 

COINSCHEDULE.COM strictly protects the security of your personal information and honours your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in England or any other country where COINSCHEDULE.COM, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located. 

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others. 

**ENFORCEMENT**  
If for some reason you believe COINSCHEDULE.COM has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words “Privacy Policy” are in the Subject line. 

**COOKIES**  
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer / device. 

Cookies are small files saved to the user's computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. 

Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors. 

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [ <http://www.google.com/privacy.html> ]. 

Other cookies may be stored to your computer’s hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected. 

**USER PROFILES**  
As mentioned above, every registered user has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification number, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile. 

When you register, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie. This cookie is uniquely yours. It is your passport to seamless travel across www.coinschedule.com, allowing you to download free material, order free newsletters, check the latest ICOs, receive alerts and so on, without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won't have to re-register – just use your Registration ID to identify yourself. 

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**  
When you join us, you provide us with your contact information and email address. We use this information to uniquely identify you. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including marketing and ad services, blog articles and newsletters. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. The above-mentioned third-party ad service providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies in connection with advertisements offered through this and other websites, including helping to operate ad networks. Click on the links to find out more about their practices, for opting-out and for any other choices they provide to you:   
<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>

We may also share information about you as follows: 

* With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to your information to carry out work on our behalf. These service providers help with our business operations such as fraud prevention and technology services.
* When we believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of your information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of or enforce our user agreements or other policies and agreements.

 ** _Last Update: March 3rd, 2018_**
